sweetness-light.com 2012-12-30

# Privacy Policy | Sweetness & Light

> Sweetness & Light will not disclose your private information to any third party except if required to do so by law, or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with legal process, respond to claims, or to protect the rights, property or safety of Sweetness & Light users or the public. Sweetness & Light takes all reasonable care in handling your personal information to ensure its security both offline and online.
> 
> **Types of Information Collected**
> 
> You are free to browse Sweetness & Light without submitting any personal information at all. Your IP address (current internet address) is stored in server logs at the time of your visit, as it is on all web sites. Sweetness & Light does not collect any personal information (such as a name, address or e-mail address) when you visit the site unless you register to the site or provide the information when leaving a comment.
> 
> **Posting Comments on Articles**
> 
> It is important to remember that when you provide personal information (e.g., last name, address, phone number) in an online post such information is visible to anyone and may be used by someone in a manner unintended by you. For that reason you are discouraged from posting any personal information on this site.
> 
> **Cookies**
> 
> Sweetness & Light’s software uses browser cookies to keep track of which messages you have read, and other information about your session. Cookies are small pieces of text that are stored on your hard drive between visits. For example, cookies store your user name and password when you post comments so you don’t have to re-enter them each time you visit. These cookies do not collect, store or maintain any private, personally identifiable information. You do not have to accept cookies to visit or use this site, although turning cookies off may limit the site’s functionality. You can choose to refuse the cookies, delete the cookies from your hard drive or turn off cookies at any time by updating your browser’s preferences.
> 
> **Ad Servers**
> 
> We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit S&L. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies go [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).
